A Guide to the Records of the Office of the Executive Vice-President, William E. Lavery, 1968-1974
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
Records of the Office of the Executive Vice-President, William E. Lavery, 1968-1974
Special Collections, Virginia Tech, Blacksburg, Va.
RG 4/3
28 Cubic Feet; 20 boxes
This collection contains correspondence and other official records of Lavery during his year as Executive Vice-President before becoming President of the University. Collection includes materials concerning budget matters, Board of Visitors, Computing Center, Computer Science, Community Colleges, each of the Colleges, Building Committee, Institutional Research, Task Force for Innovative Approaches to Instruction, University Council and Commissions, V.P.I. Industry Center, and Virginia Public Telecommunications Council.
Lavery, William Edward
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Acquisition Information
This collection was transferred to Special Collections.
Administrative Note
The position of Executive Vice-President was established in 1968 as a result of the reorganization of the University's top-level administration. Lavery was the last of three individuals to hold the position before its elimination in 1974. William Lavery became the President of Virginia Polytechnic Institute that same year, serving until the end of 1987. His records as for this period are not yet available.
Scope and Content
This collection contains correspondence and other official records of Lavery during his year as Executive Vice-President before becoming President of the University. Collection includes materials concerning budget matters, Board of Visitors, Computing Center, Computer Science, Community Colleges, each of the Colleges, Building Committee, Institutional Research, Task Force for Innovative Approaches to Instruction, University Council and Commissions, V.P.I. Industry Center, and Virginia Public Telecommunications Council.
Arrangement
This collection is in its original order.
Adjunct Descriptive Data
Related Materials
Records of the Office of the President, William E. Lavery, 1975-1987
Records of the Office of the Vice President and the Office of the Executive Vice-President, Warren W. Brandt, RG 3/4
Records of the Office of the Executive Vice-President, William J. McKeefery, RG 4/2
Index Terms
Persons:
Lavery, William Edward
Organizations:
Virginia Polytechnic Institute; Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University
Subjects:
Faculty; University Archives; University History
Contents List
- General Correspondence, 1968-1974
  - NWL - Dahlgren Program (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - DSP-66 Exchange visitor Program, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Purchase Oders, etc., 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Staff Meeting Agendas, 1968-1970 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Dr T. M. Hahn Jr., 1968-1970 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Division Budget, 1968-1970 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Quarterly Allotment Estimates, 1968-1970 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Administrative Intern Reports, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Dormitories, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Dormitories, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Board of Visitors, 1968-1970 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Personnel (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Financial Statements, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Financial Statements, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Financial Statements, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Budget, 1976-1978 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Chart of Accounts (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Allotment Forms (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Operating Allotments #1, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Operating Allotments #2, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Operating Allotments #3, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Operating Allotments #4, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Operating Allotments #5, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Purchase Orders, Requisitions, etc. #1, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Purchase Orders, Requisitions, etc. #2, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Allotments/General Administration #1, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Allotments/General Administration #2, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - University Council Agenda, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - University Council, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - University Council #1a, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - University Council #1b, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - University Council #2a, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - University Council #2b, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - University Council, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - University council General Correspondence, 1969-1971 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Faculty Senate #1, 1968-1974 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Faculty Senate #2, 1968-1974 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Commission on Faculty Affairs, 1972-1974 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Commission on Student Affairs #1, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Commission on Student Affairs #2, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Commission on Student Affairs #1, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Commission on Student Affairs #2, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Commission on Undergraduate Studies #1, 1970-1974 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Commission on Undergraduate Studies #2, 1970-1974 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Commission on Research and Graduate Studies #1, 1972-1974 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Commission on Research and Graduate Studies #2, 1972-1974 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Computer Committee, 1968-1970 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - General Assembly of the Virginia House Appropriations Committee Staff Report, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Affirmative Action Program Section for State Plan, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Budget Information #1, 1970-1972 to 1974-1976. (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Budget Information #2, 1970-1972 to 1974-1976. (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Budget Information #3, 1970-1972 to 1974-1976. (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Budget Information #4, 1970-1972 to 1974-1976. (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Transparencies - Enrollment Projections, 1973-1982 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Accounting General, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Divisionof the Budget (Rich.), 1974 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Budget and Allotments, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Federal Funding, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Financial Reports, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Administration - Staff Mtg, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Department of Health, Education and Welfare, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Administration - Self-Study, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Administrative Space, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Rural Development Act of 1972, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Governor's Office, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Correspondence with Senate and House of Delegations, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - President - T.M. Hahn, Jr., 1974 (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Executive Vice President, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Vice President/ Academic Affairs, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Vice President/ Administration, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - International Program, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - Special Academic Programs, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - Health and Safety Office, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - Vice President/ Student Affairs, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - Executive Assistant to President, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 76)
  - Budget Director, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 77)
  - Business Manager, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 78)
  - General Counsel, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 79)
  - Graduate Studies, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 80)
  - Alumni Association - General, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 81)
  - Athletic Association - General, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 82)
  - Bookstore/ Auxiliary Ent., 1974 (Box 4, Folder 83)
  - Dining Halls/ Auxiliary Ent., 1974 (Box 4, Folder 84)
  - Dormitories/ Auxiliary Ent., 1974 (Box 4, Folder 85)
  - Auxiliary Ent. - General, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 86)
  - Motor Pool/ Auxiliary Ent., 1974 (Box 4, Folder 87)
  - Airport/ Auxiliary Ent., 1974 (Box 4, Folder 88)
  - Awards, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 89)
  - Board of Visitors General Correspondence (Box 4, Folder 90)
  - Board Reports, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 91)
  - Building and Grounds, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 92)
  - Appalachian - FPC, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 93)
  - Projects and Budgets Capital Outlay, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 94)
  - Capital Outlay Requests, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 95)
  - College of Agriculture, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 96)
  - College of Architecture, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 97)
  - College of Arts and Sciences, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 98)
  - College of Business, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 99)
  - College of Education, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 100)
  - College of Engineering, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 101)
  - College of Home Economics, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 101)
  - University Library Committee, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 103)
  - Veterinary Medicine #1, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 104)
  - Veterinary Medicine #2, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 105)
  - Graduate School, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 106)
  - Learning Resources Center, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 107)
  - Dissertations - Grad. Stdnts., 1974 (Box 5, Folder 108)
  - Building Committee, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 109)
  - University Committees General, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 110)
  - Computer Committee, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 111)
  - Managerial Subcommittee of Computer Science, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 112)
  - Patent Committee #1, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 113)
  - Patent Committee #2, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 114)
  - Presidential Search, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 115)
  - Judicial Review Committee Appeals #1, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 116)
  - Judicial Review Committee Appeals #2, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 117)
  - Judicial Review Committee General, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 118)
  - Traffic Appeals Subcommittee, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 119)
  - Community College System, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 120)
  - Computer Allotments Computing Center, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 121)
  - Continuing Education Center, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 122)
  - Extension Division, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 123)
  - Computing Center, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 124)
  - Division of ADP, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 125)
  - EDUCOM, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 126)
  - Farmsnet, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 127)
  - Preston Project, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 128)
  - State Technical Services, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 129)
  - Information Division, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 130)
  - Research Division, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 131)
  - Proposals, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 132)
  - Center for Environmental Stds., 1974 (Box 5, Folder 133)
  - Wooden Pallet Research Center, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 134)
  - Forest Products Res. Center, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 135)
  - Glee Club, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 136)
  - Institutional Research, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 137)
  - Long-Range Planning, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 138)
  - Student Enrollment Projections, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 139)
  - Inventory System, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 140)
  - Library, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 141)
  - Dean's Meetings, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 142)
  - Administrator's Conference, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 143)
  - National Association of State Universities and Land-Grant Colleges, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 144)
  - System's Development, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 145)
  - Land-Grant College Meeting, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 146)
  - Miscellaneous, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 147)
  - Congratulatory Letters, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 148)
  - County Leaders Planning Conf., 1974 (Box 5, Folder 149)
  - General, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 150)
  - National Association of College and University Business Oficers, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 151)
  - Business Officers Council, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 152)
  - Phi Delta Kappa, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 153)
  - Southern Association of Colleges and Schools, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 154)
  - Omicron Delta Kappa, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 155)
  - Association of Virginia Colleges, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 156)
  - Virginia Agribusiness Council, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 157)
  - Dismissals - Personnel, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 158)
  - Employee Benefits, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 159)
  - Insurance, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 160)
  - Executive Information System - Personnel/ Payroll/ Retirement Subsystems, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 161)
  - Faculty Saleries, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 162)
  - Personnel/ General, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 163)
  - EEO #1, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 164)
  - EEO #2, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 165)
  - Job Applications, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 166)
  - Faculty Tenure and Promotion, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 167)
  - Letters of Recommendation, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 168)
  - TIAA - CREF, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 169)
  - Faculty Grievances, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 170)
  - Physical Plant Planning, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 171)
  - Policy, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 172)
  - Travel, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 173)
  - Purchasing, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 174)
  - Grants and Proposals - General, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 175)
  - Grants and Proposals, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 176)
  - National Science Foundation Grants, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 177)
  - Contracts - SREB, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 178)
  - Eminent Scholars, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 179)
  - Council of Higher Education, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 180)
  - Finance Advisory Board, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 181)
  - SCHEV - The VA Plan, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 182)
  - Finance Advisory Board Budget Subcommittee, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 183)
  - General Professional Advisory Council, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 184)
  - Central Virginia Consortium, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 185)
  - Tidewater Consortium for Continuing Education, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 186)
  - Northern Virginia Consortium, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 187)
  - Western Region Consortium, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 188)
  - Admissions and Registrar, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 189)
  - Commencement, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 190)
  - Co-op Program, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 191)
  - Disruptive Activities, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 192)
  - Student Affairs, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 193)
  - Honor Court, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 194)
  - Infirmary, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 195)
  - Residence Hall Federation, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 196)
  - ROTC, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 197)
  - Student Budget Board, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 198)
  - Student Budget Board - General, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 199)
  - Student Life Policies, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 200)
  - Student Center Budget, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 201)
  - Student Fees, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 202)
  - Student Government Association, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 203)
  - Scholarships, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 204)
  - Student Loans, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 205)
  - Student Organizations, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 206)
  - Student Records System, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 207)
  - Student Center, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 208)
  - Civilian Marching Band, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 209)
  - Student Publications, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 210)
  - Crisis Center, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 211)
  - Fraternity - Sorority System, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 212)
  - Town of Blacksburg, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 213)
  - Treasurer's Office, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 214)
  - University Developement, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 215)
  - Virginia Public Telecommunications Council (VPTC), 1974 (Box 7, Folder 216)
  - Consulting - Approved #1, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 217)
  - Consulting - Approved #2, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 218)
  - Consulting - Approved #3, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 219)
  - Consulting - Approved #4, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 220)
  - Exchange Visitor Programs, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 221)
  - Miscellaneous Publications and Loose Papers, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 222)
- V.P. of Finance Materials, 1968-1971
  - Accounting - Automated Accounting System (Box 7, Folder 223)
  - Accounting - Financial Reports (Box 7, Folder 224)
  - Accounting - Accounting Office General (Box 7, Folder 225)
  - Accounting - Purchacing Orders, Requisitions (Box 7, Folder 226)
  - Accounting - Quarterly Allotment Estimates (Box 7, Folder 227)
  - Accounting Budgets - Appropriations, Budgetary Items (Box 7, Folder 228)
  - Accounting Budgets - Biennial Budget - 1970-72 Division of Budget Corres (Box 7, Folder 229)
  - Accounting Budgets - Biennial Budget - 1970-72 Appropriations (Box 7, Folder 230)
  - Accounting Budgets - Biennial Budget, 1970-72 Charts, Tables, Forms, etc (Box 7, Folder 231)
  - Accounting Budgets - Biennial Budget, 1970-72 General Correspondence (Box 7, Folder 232)
  - Accounting Budgets - Yearly Budget, 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 233)
  - Accounting Budgets - Budgets and Allotments (General) (Box 7, Folder 234)
  - Accounting Budgets - Division of the Budget in Richmond (Box 7, Folder 235)
  - Accounting Budgets - Governor's Budget Advisory Board (Box 7, Folder 236)
  - Accounting Budgets - Comptroller's Office in Richmond (Box 7, Folder 237)
  - Administration - Staff Meeting Material (Box 7, Folder 238)
  - Administration - General (Civil Rights, etc.) (Box 7, Folder 239)
  - Administration - Governor's Management Study Team (Box 7, Folder 240)
  - Administration - Legislation (Box 7, Folder 241)
  - Administration - Self-Study (Box 7, Folder 242)
  - Administration - Space (Box 7, Folder 243)
  - Administration - Governor's Office (Box 7, Folder 244)
  - Administration - President Hahn (Box 7, Folder 245)
  - Administration - Pres. Visits to Departments (Box 8, Folder 246)
  - Administration - Vice Pres. Acad. Aff (Box 8, Folder 247)
  - Administration - Administrative Interns (Box 8, Folder 248)
  - Administration - Business Manager (Box 8, Folder 249)
  - Administration - Exec. Asst. to Pres (Box 8, Folder 250)
  - Administration - VP Student Affairs (Box 8, Folder 251)
  - Administration - VP Finance (Box 8, Folder 252)
  - Administration - VP Administration (Box 8, Folder 253)
  - Administration - Executive Vice Pres (Box 8, Folder 254)
  - Alumni Association - General (Box 8, Folder 255)
  - Articles and Publications - General (Box 8, Folder 256)
  - Articles and Publications - Annual Report (Box 8, Folder 257)
  - Athletic Association - General (Box 8, Folder 258)
  - Auxiliary Enterprises - Airport (Box 8, Folder 259)
  - Auxiliary Enterprises - Book Store (Box 8, Folder 260)
  - Auxiliary Enterprises - Campus Bus Service (Box 8, Folder 261)
  - Auxiliary Enterprises - Centralized Mailing (Box 8, Folder 262)
  - Auxiliary Enterprises - Dormitories (Box 8, Folder 263)
  - Auxiliary Enterprises - Electric Service Department (Box 8, Folder 264)
  - Auxiliary Enterprises - Dining Halls - Food Services (Box 8, Folder 265)
  - Auxiliary Enterprises - General (Box 8, Folder 266)
  - Auxiliary Enterprises - Motor Pool (Box 8, Folder 267)
  - Auxiliary Enterprises - Laundry (Box 8, Folder 268)
  - Board of Visitors - General (Box 8, Folder 269)
  - Board of Visitors - Board Reports (Box 8, Folder 270)
  - Buildings and Grounds - General (Box 8, Folder 271)
  - Capital Outlay - General (Box 8, Folder 272)
  - Colleges - Agriculture (Box 8, Folder 273)
  - Colleges - Architecture (Box 8, Folder 274)
  - Colleges - Arts and Sciences (Box 8, Folder 275)
  - Colleges - Business (Box 8, Folder 276)
  - Colleges - Education (Box 8, Folder 277)
  - Colleges - Engineering (Box 8, Folder 278)
  - Colleges - Home Economics (Box 8, Folder 279)
  - Colleges - Graduate School (Box 8, Folder 280)
  - Colleges - Learning Resources Center (Box 8, Folder 281)
  - Colleges - Summer School (Box 8, Folder 282)
  - Committees - Building Committee (Box 8, Folder 283)
  - Committees - Computer Committee (Box 8, Folder 284)
  - Committees - Health Services Committee (Box 8, Folder 285)
  - Committees - Home Economics Group II (Box 8, Folder 286)
  - Committees - General (Box 8, Folder 287)
  - Committees - Homecoming Committee (Box 8, Folder 288)
  - Committees - Library Committee (Box 8, Folder 289)
  - Committees - Patent Committee (Box 8, Folder 290)
  - Committees - Student Activities Committee (Box 9, Folder 291)
  - Computing Center- Administrative Systems (Box 9, Folder 292)
  - Computing Center - Computer Allotments (Box 9, Folder 293)
  - Computing Center - General (Box 9, Folder 294)
  - Computing Center - Data Processing (Box 9, Folder 295)
  - Computing Cneter - EDUCOM (Box 9, Folder 296)
  - Computing Center - Management Information System (Box 9, Folder 297)
  - Computing Center - Payroll System (Box 9, Folder 298)
  - Computing Center - Regional Computing Center (Box 9, Folder 299)
  - Computing Center - Reorganization (Box 9, Folder 300)
  - Computing Center - Terminals (Box 9, Folder 301)
  - Computing Center - FARMSNET (Box 9, Folder 302)
  - Computing Center - Computer Consultants (Box 9, Folder 303)
  - Computing Center - Equipment Aquisition Approval (Box 9, Folder 304)
  - Computing Center - Salaries (Box 9, Folder 305)
  - Computing Center - Control Data Corporation (Box 9, Folder 306)
  - Computing Center - Extension General (Box 9, Folder 307)
  - Divisions - Extension CEC (Box 9, Folder 308)
  - Divisions - Extension Reston (Box 9, Folder 309)
  - Divisions - Extension State Technical Services (Box 9, Folder 310)
  - Divisions - Extension, Task Force on Extension (Box 9, Folder 311)
  - Divisions - Information (Box 9, Folder 312)
  - Divisions - General Research (Box 9, Folder 313)
  - Divisions - Research Law Enforcement (Box 9, Folder 314)
  - Divisions - Research Proposals (Box 9, Folder 315)
  - Divisions - Research, Research Counsel (Box 9, Folder 316)
  - Divisions - Research, VPI Industry Center (Box 9, Folder 317)
  - Divisions - Center for Environmental Studies (Box 9, Folder 318)
  - Glee Club - General (Box 9, Folder 319)
  - Institutional Research - General (Box 9, Folder 320)
  - Library - General (Box 9, Folder 321)
  - Meetings - Dean's Meetings (Box 9, Folder 322)
  - Meetings - Fall Administrators' Conference (Box 10, Folder 323)
  - Meetngs - Land-Grant College Meetings (Box 9, Folder 324)
  - Meetings - Off-Campus Planning Program '69 (Box 10, Folder 325)
  - Miscellaneous - Architectual Concerns (Box 10, Folder 326)
  - Miscellaneous - Congratulatory Letters (Box 10, Folder 327)
  - Miscellaneous - County Leaders Planning Conf (Box 10, Folder 328)
  - Miscellaneous - University of Florida Consulting (Box 10, Folder 329)
  - Personnel - Job Applicants (Box 10, Folder 330)
  - Personnel - State Division of Personnel (Box 10, Folder 331)
  - Personnel - Faculty Salaries (Box 10, Folder 332)
  - Personnel - General (Box 10, Folder 333)
  - Personnel - Dismissals (Box 10, Folder 334)
  - Organizations - Rotary Club (Box 10, Folder 335)
  - Organizations - NACUBO (Box 10, Folder 336)
  - Organizations - Blacksburg Community Federation (Box 10, Folder 337)
  - Miscellaneous - Virginia State Merger (Box 10, Folder 338)
  - Miscellaneous - SCATS (Box 10, Folder 339)
  - Miscellaneous - Mission to El Salvador (Box 10, Folder 340)
  - Special Funding - Geochronological Lab (Box 10, Folder 341)
  - Special Funding - Geology Grant (Box 10, Folder 342)
  - Special Funding - Contracts Signed (Box 10, Folder 343)
  - Purchasing - General (Box 10, Folder 344)
  - Policy - General (Box 10, Folder 345)
  - Physical Plant Planning - General (Box 10, Folder 346)
  - Personnel - President's Wage Price Freeze (Box 10, Folder 347)
  - Personnel - Life Insurance (Box 10, Folder 348)
  - Personnel - Unemployment (Box 10, Folder 349)
  - Personnel - Letters of Recommendation (Box 10, Folder 350)
  - Personnel - Automated Payroll System (Box 10, Folder 351)
  - State Council of Higher Education - General (Box 10, Folder 352)
  - Special Funding - VPI Educational Foundation (SKC) (Box 10, Folder 353)
  - Special Funding - Veterinary Science (Ohio State, School, etc.) (Box 10, Folder 354)
  - Special Funding - Chemistry Development Grant (Box 10, Folder 355)
  - Special Funding - Overhead Rates (Box 10, Folder 356)
  - Special Funding - Gift Campaign (Box 10, Folder 357)
  - Special Funding - Nuclear Reactor (Box 10, Folder 358)
  - Special Funding - Private Grants (Box 10, Folder 359)
  - Special Funding - NSF Grants (Box 10, Folder 360)
  - Special Funding - Grants & Proposals General (Box 10, Folder 361)
  - Student Affairs - Admissions and Registrar, General Student Affairs, 1968-1974 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Student Affairs - Commencement, 1968-1971 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Student Affairs - Co-op Program, 1968-1971 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Student Affairs - Disruptive Activities, 1968-1971 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Student Affairs - General, 1968-1971 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Student Affairs - Infirmary, 1968-1971 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Student Affairs - ROTC, 1968-1971 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Student Affairs - Scholarship, 1968-1971 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Student Affairs - Student Budget Board, 1968-1971 (Box 18, Folder 9-10)